seoautomatic.com 2009-09-08

# Privacy & Legal | Search Commander, Inc.

Privacy Policy of Search Commander, Inc  
Effective from 31st of January 2008 to 30th of January 2009.

**General Information **  
Search Commander, Inc takes your privacy seriously. If you do too, please read the following information to learn more about our privacy practices, and don’t hesitate to ask for any clarification.

  * This policy covers what personally identifiable information Search Commander, Inc collects and how it is treated. Personally identifiable information is information that can be used to identify visitors to the http://www.searchcommander.com Web Site. This information may be limited to an IP address or extend to personally identifiable information such as your name, address, email address, or phone number.
  * This policy only applies to http://www.searchcommander.com and does not extend to the practices of other Web Sites that we may link to, companies that we do not own or control, or to people that we do not employ or manage.

* * *

**Contact Information **  
We invite you to [contact us](http://www.searchcommander.com/contact/) if you have questions about this privacy policy.

**Search Commander, Inc  
11124 NE Halsey St. #481  
Portland 97220  
OR United States **

* * *

**Dispute Resolution **  
Search Commander, Inc is committed to resolving any dispute you may have regarding our privacy policy quickly and efficiently.Disputes will be handled by our customer service representative as outlined at [http://www.searchcommander.com](http://www.searchcommander.com//). Our customer service will promptly correct any errors.Search Commander, Inc is [P3PSeal](http://www.p3pseal.com/verify.php?sid=016AF02217) certified. In the event that a dispute regarding our privacy practices cannot be settled through our normal dispute resolution processes, you should contact [P3PSeal](http://www.p3pseal.com/), an independent third party. P3PSeal will serve as a liaison with Search Commander, Inc to resolve any dispute you may have.

* * *

**Information Collection **  
When visiting Web Sites certain information about you and your computer can sometimes be collected. This section explains what information Search Commander, Inc collects, and how it is used.Information Collected – What information do we collect and why?We collect the following identifiable information about our visitors:

  * dynamic.clickstream
  * dynamic.http
  * dynamic.searchtext
  * dynamic.miscdata

We collect identifiable information for the following reasons:

  * Web Site and System Administration

Our Web Site generates server log files automatically. These log files are used to generate statistical information and error reports to ensure the Web Site runs with a minimum of disruption. They are not actively used to identify individual visitors.

* * *

Information Recipients – Who has access to the information collected?

  * Ourselves and/or our entities acting as our agents or entities for which we are acting as an agent.

* * *

Information Retention – How long is this information retained?We do not retain information for this area of the Web Site.
